{
    "id": "19b7d00fb6f0412fbcc63d2f2ce98205",
    "title": "Comparatives exercise",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "646cb114a3524a2fa7c9217244960aeb",
            "title": "Comparatives Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Your car is ………………… .. than mine.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "more small",
                        "smaller"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "My house is ……………………… than yours.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "bigger",
                        "biggest"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "You should write ……………………… than you do.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "oftener",
                        "more often",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "It is ………………… than you think.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "easier",
                        "more easy"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "The baby is ………………… ugly than you.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "less",
                        "lesser"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I have got …………………. energy than I used to have.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "less",
                        "fewer"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "This is ……………………… than that.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "commoner",
                        "more common",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "He is ………………….. than stupid.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "more lazy",
                        "lazier",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Her boyfriend is ………………… than her.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "much old",
                        "much older",
                        "more old"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "He is ………………… than he looks.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "cleverer",
                        "more clever"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}